// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "India played its first one day in ?",
    answer: "1974",
    options: [
      "1970",
      "1971",
      "1972",
      "1974"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "________was India’s first One-day captain",
    answer: "Ajit Wadekar",
    options: [
      "Sunil Gavaskar",
      "Ajit Wadekar",
      "Kapil dev",
      "Manoj prabhakar"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The length of the pitch is:",
    answer: "twenty two yards",
    options: [
      "twenty yards",
      "twenty two yards",
      "twenty one yards",
      "twenty three yards"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The ‘Laws of Cricket’ were drawn up in:",
    answer: "1744",
    options: [
      "1740",
      "1746",
      "1744",
      "1742"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The game of cricket traces its origin from ___",
    answer: "England",
    options: [
      "England",
      "Mumbai",
      "India",
      "Pakistan"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Where is Chepauk?",
    answer: "Cricket stadium in Chennai",
    options: [
      "Cricket ground in Champaran",
      "An almost circular stadium in Iceland",
      "Cricket stadium in Chennai",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Indian cricket originated in",
    answer: "Bombay (Mumbal)",
    options: [
      "Mysore",
      "Chennal",
      "Calcutta (Kolkata)",
      "Bombay (Mumbal)"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Indian played first test match against ________ .",
    answer: "England",
    options: [
      "South Africa",
      "Pakistan",
      "England",
      "Australia"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Indian played their First T20 Match against _______.",
    answer: "South Africa",
    options: [
      "England",
      "South Africa",
      "Pakistan",
      "Australia"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following is first cricket club in India ?",
    answer: "Oriental Cricket Club",
    options: [
      "Maharashtra Cricket Club",
      "East Indian Cricket Club",
      "Bombay Cricket Club",
      "Oriental Cricket Club"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];